Personal details

<mark>Name</mark> Kristi Järve

Address
Preston, PR3

Email

valgeroos@gmail.com

Languages

English

Kristi Järve

I'm a proactive and enthusiastic professional with a knack for teamwork and leadership. My experience has honed my ability to excel both in team settings and independently, particularly in high-pressure environments where meeting deadlines is crucial. Communication is a strong suit of mine, and I thrive on learning new skills and knowledge, which I love to share with my colleagues. My blend of logical, critical, and creative thinking inspired my journey to becoming a certified Full Stack Web and Software Developer and Designer, a path where I continuously grow and contribute effectively.

Work experience

Digital Marketing Assistant

Mar 2023 - Present

UK Carline Limited, Bilsborrow, Preston, Lancashire

- · Enhance advertising and customer journey processes through analysis and programming.
- Develop marketing strategies and create digital materials, including email and social media layouts.
- · Utilize Google Analytics, Tag Manager, and other software for monitoring website improvements.
- · Collaborate with Marketing, Sales, and senior management to strategize and implement campaigns.
- Proficient in Python, JavaScript, HTML, with further training in Vue.js, Docker, AWS, PHP Laravel.
- Knowledgeable in digital marketing tools like Mailchimp and social media platforms.
- Design marketing materials and optimize website efficiency.
- Create data-driven dashboards and collaborate with Web and CRM Developers on new technologies.

Customer Support Administrator

Jul 2017 - Mar 2023

UK Carline Ltd, Bilsborrow, Preston, Lancashire

- Processing customer's financial applications, ensuring accuracy of the information and in line with our data protection policies.
- Established warm and friendly rapport whilst interacting with customers by phone and email whilst resolving customer queries.
- Raising, checking, sending and submitting lease agreements and other financial documentation in accordance with the Data Protection Act and FCA.
- · Managing my workflow and workload from start to finish with a high level of accuracy of data input.
- Liaising with car manufacturers and suppliers, ensuring out vehicle orders are processed correctly, for a smooth and prompt vehicle deliveries.
- Demonstrated expertise in Google Sheets and associated applications to manage data effectively.
- Contributed to improving web user experience and conversion goals through compelling design and website programming.

Debt Recovery Officer

Mar 2017 - Jul 2017

Guardian Recovery, Preston, Lancashire

- Interviewed customers to determine reasons for delinquency, source of income and next pay date to build solutions for financial issues.
- Met demands of busy collections group by performing high volume of daily calls.
- Used emotional intelligence to understand the emotional state of the client and manage my personal emotions in order to exercise the right social skills.
- Liaised with debt recovery agents or solicitors regarding outstanding accounts.

Senior Customer Adviser

Sep 2015 - Mar 2017

Skipton Building Society, Skipton, North Yorkshire

- · Resolved customer questions, issues and complaints efficiently to reach mutually beneficial solutions.
- Kept detailed records of customer interactions for future reference.
- Improved service quality and increased sales by developing strong knowledge of company's products and services.
- Supervised customer service representatives, assessed performance and organised development plans to diminish process lags.
- Mentored junior team members on methods on industry best practices for outstanding service and retention.
- Completed frequent assessments of training materials, structure and success rates in order to enhance programme.

Cash On Go Ltd., Tallinn, Harjumaa

- Explored and created new ways to resolve problems with processes, technology or team members to improve overall efficiency.
- Maintained regular email and telephone contact with customers to appropriately manage overdue account payments.
- Received and resolved customer queries efficiently, enabling timely invoice processing and payment.
- Scrutinized debtor balances to avoid late payments and bad debt, attaining financial stability objectives.
- Submitted credit and loan applications to underwriters to verify income, assets and debt, assessing qualifications for exact amount granted.

Assistant Quality Coach

Oct 2013 - Jul 2014

Microsoft Xbox Project/ Arvato Services Estonia OÜ, Tallinn, ArvatoHarjumaa

- Checked employees performance to guarantee compliance with process standards.
- Maintained quality management structure by conducting continuous reviews.
- Evaluated component materials against paperwork.
- Provided additional materials to enhance training.
- Developed long-term training strategies for new and existing employees to apply best practices.
- Documented participant attendance, engagement and progress.
- Mentored learners to build subject confidence and competence.
- Met individual needs through attentive, student-centred training approaches.

SKILLS

- Certified Full Stack Website and Software Developer: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Bootstrap, Git, SQL, API, PHP, JQuery, Java, AJAX, MySQL etc.
- · Logical and systematic thinking
- · Creative design and strategies
- Calm and level-headed in difficult and stressful situations
- Technical computer knowledge
- Customer needs analysis
- · Multi-tasking and quick learner
- Proactive team player, project managing and managing own workload.

Certified Training completed in:

- Managerial Course
- · Certified First Aid
- Data Protection Act 1998
- Specialist Automotive Finance (SAF) 2024
- Money Laundering Regulations 2007
- Consumer Credit Act 1974
- TCF (Treating Customers Fairly)
- FCA (Financial Conduct Authority)
- PRA (Prudential Regulation Authority)
- · AML (Anti-Money Laundering) training
- · CIFAS warnings check training

Education

GCSEs Jun 2010